<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kompare.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Kompare</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Kompare</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Kompare</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Kompare</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Kompare</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kompare</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Kompare</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKomparexx</name>
  <summary>Diff/Patch Frontend</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Interfaz para diff/patch</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Interface para o Diff/Patch</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Rozhranie Diff/Patch</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Začelje za diff/patch</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Gränssnitt för Diff/Patch</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Оболонка до Diff/Patch</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxDiff/Patch Frontendxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Kompare is a GUI front-end program that enables differences between source files to be viewed and merged. It can be used to compare differences on files or the contents of folders, and it supports a variety of diff formats and provide many options to customize the information level displayed.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Kompare es un programa de interfaz gráfica de usuario que permite ver y fusionar las diferencias entre archivos de código fuente. Se puede usar para comparar las diferencias entre archivos o del contenido de carpetas. Permite distintos formatos de «diff» y proporciona muchas opciones para personalizar el nivel de información que muestra.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Kompare é um programa gráfico que permite a visualização e reunião de diferenças entre ficheiros de código. Poderá ser usado para comparar as diferenças nos ficheiros ou no conteúdo das pastas, suportando uma grande variedade de formatos de diferença e oferecendo muitas opções para personalizar o nível de informação apresentado.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Kompare je GUI frontendový program, ktorý povolí zmeny medzi zdrojovými súbormi zobraziť a zlúčiť. Môže sa použiť na porovnanie rozdielov v súboroch alebo obsahu adresárov a podporuje škálu diff formátov a poskytuje mnoho volieb na prispôsobenie zobrazenej úrovne informácií.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Kompare je grafični uporabniški vmesnik za diff/patch, ki omogoča prikaz in združevanje razlik med datotekami. Lahko ga uporabite za primerjavo razlik med datotekami ali vsebino map, podpira pa tudi številne vrste razlik in možnosti za prilagoditev stopnje prikazanih podrobnosti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kompare är ett grafiskt gränssnittsprogram som gör det möjligt att visa och sammanfoga skillnader mellan källkodsfiler. Det kan användas för att jämföra skillnader mellan filer och innehållet i kataloger, och det stöder en mängd olika jämförelseformat, och tillhandahåller många alternativ för att anpassa informationsnivån som visas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Kompare є програмою — графічним інтерфейсом користувача, за допомогою якої ви можете переглядати різницю між текстами файлів та об’єднувати тексти файлів. Kompare можна використовувати для порівняння вмісту як файлів, так і тек. У Kompare передбачено підтримку багатьох різних форматів різниці між файлами, у цій програми передбачено багато параметрів, за допомогою яких ви зможете налаштувати рівень показу інформації.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKompare is a GUI front-end program that enables differences between source files to be viewed and merged. It can be used to compare differences on files or the contents of folders, and it supports a variety of diff formats and provide many options to customize the information level displayed.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Funciones:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Comparing differences on files or the contents of folders recursively.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Comparación de diferencias entre archivos o del contenido de carpetas (recursivamente).</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Comparação das diferenças nos ficheiros ou no conteúdo recursivo de pastas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Porovnávanie rozdielov v súboroch alebo obsah priečinkov rekurzívne.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Primerjava razlik med datotekami ali vsebinami map.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Jämför skillnader mellan filer eller innehållet i kataloger rekursivt.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Порівняння окремих файлів або вмісту цілих тек рекурсивно.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxComparing differences on files or the contents of folders recursively.xx</li>
      <li>Supports a variety of diff formats and provides many options to customize the information level displayed.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Permite distintos formatos de «diff» y proporciona muchas opciones para personalizar el nivel de información que muestra.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta uma variedade de formatos de ajuda e oferece muitas opções para personalizar o nível de informação apresentado.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podporuje škálu diff formátov a poskytuje mnoho volieb na prispôsobenie zobrazenej úrovne informácií.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Podpira številne vrste razlik in ponuja številne možnosti za prilagoditev stopnje prikazanih podrobnosti.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder en mängd olika jämförelseformat, och tillhandahåller många alternativ för att anpassa informationsnivån som visas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">У Kompare передбачено підтримку багатьох різних форматів різниці між файлами, у цій програми передбачено багато параметрів, за допомогою яких ви зможете налаштувати рівень показу інформації.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports a variety of diff formats and provides many options to customize the information level displayed.xx</li>
      <li>Creating and applying patches.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Creación y aplicación de parches.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Criação e aplicação de modificações ('patches').</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Vytváranie a používanie záplat.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Ustvarjanje in uveljavljanje popravkov.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Skapar och inför programfixar.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Створення і накладання латок.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCreating and applying patches.xx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kompare.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">http://kde.org/applications/development/kompare/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kompare</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kompare</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kompare</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
